Okay, okay, let's all calm down.
You're not getting away this time.
You naughty laundry.
Hm?
I wonder what that is.
It's awfully beautiful.
Well, I can't go beyond
Oh my gosh.
手間苦しいステージでその絡まった感動
満足いくまで何回も壊してしまう
運命にとらえきさえ彷徨う明日は
雨の手を選んで何を手放しひとつになればいいんだよ
I love mycourse
dataset I家
but mulch
until this episode
sent me
but
You're scrunchie.
She still has it.
You remember.
To tell you the truth, I've known for a while now.
Ever since our last battle.
He do it!
Mama is here.
Hang on, He do it.
It hurt so much.
Like my heart was being torn into a thousand pieces.
But even through all that pain, I kept thinking,
I won't forget them.
He do it.
But I knew what it meant to lose you.
And I knew that pain would be even worse.
I won't be alone!
Welcome back!
But wait, if you remembered, then why didn't you tell us sooner?
Because I wanted my wish to come true.
Because I wanted to win.
The wish itself didn't matter.
If I won enough, Yuzuki would complete the oath again like she did with Hanayo.
And then she'd be freed from the card.
That's right, isn't it?
What are you saying, Ito-e?
That wouldn't solve anything!
You'd end up like me!
I'm flattered you care so much, but please don't worry about me.
I don't see this as a bad thing.
In fact, it's more like a dream come true.
Being with friends, making a noble sacrifice to save them.
It's all just so romantic.
I'm happy such a beautiful thing even exists.
Of course, the battles and stuff are incredible, but meeting the two of you, seeing what real friendship is like, to me, that's, I guess, it's like a miracle.
Finding a friend who can do something important for you, and being able to give something back to that friend?
If I have that, then there's not a single wish in the world I need.
Ito-e!
Doing something for a friend.
Please, Tama.
Will you finally listen to my wish?
Oh no.
We have to free Yuzuki from the card.
There's a chance to save my friends.
Nothing's more important than that.
I don't want you to be so sad.
If I help, will you be friends with me too?
Uh-huh.
Okay!
You tell Tama what to do.
Battling's about all I'm good for.
But if that can make your wish come true, battle and battle, as much as it takes.
Thank you, Tama.
All right, guys!
You ready?
Let's continue the match!
Oh, but Hito-e, one last thing.
I'm sorry, but there's no way I'll lose!
I've made my wish, and it's coming true!
Unko!
Attack!
Arc!
Aura!
Good game!
Good game.
I lost.
Hope that didn't hurt, Yuzuki.
Only my pride.
Oh, hey! What about your wish?
Oh, yeah! You finally figured it out?
It's clear now.
I want Yuzuki and all the other girls trapped in cards to be free.
What? Ruko, that's...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Slow down! We need to talk about this.
But we did.
You're the ones who made me realize what I needed to do.
If there's something I can do for my friends, I should do it.
Nothing would make me happier, and that's final!
I'd better be going.
Wait a sec! I'm coming with you!
Meaning we're coming.
Then, you're okay with my wish?
You're sure?
I guess so. Not like I could change your mind.
Just make sure you get your wish right, huh?
I mean, yeah, duh, I want to get out of this card.
But this'll all be for nothing if you end up as an L-Rig yourself.
We're getting dumplings on the way home, and I want you there.
So, hey, I can't wait to go shopping with you, Tama.
You know, in person.
Can we eat dumplings?
I was thinking I'd buy you some scrunchies, so you can match the rest of us.
Sounds great.
Oh, boy. Not good with heights.
I'd feel better about it if I could pick out my apartment.
Grandma.
I've been expecting you.
Hi, Ru.
Okay.
And you brought your little friends.
Yeah, what's it to you?
She is our friend, and we're here to support her.
Fine with me.
A cheering section won't make any difference.
Anything else, Ru?
A rousing speech, perhaps?
Or something you'd like to ask me?
No questions. No speeches.
All I want is to battle you.
You really are the best.
Open!
What a dark and lonely place.
Is it...
always so scary when you fight?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were all out of questions.
Ready when you are.
You're up first, Ru.
Tama, grow!
Grow.
They're both so strong.
But look at Ruko.
I know.
Something's off.
Her eyes are so cold.
I don't get this.
Battles before were always fun or exciting or something.
This is just hollow.
Hollow.
It's so quiet.
I can even hear Tama breathing.
This may be my final battle.
I can't have any doubts.
Tama, grow!
Use sword ability!
Focus.
She's one of a kind.
Gotta give her that.
Of course, you have more than enough wins to have your wish granted.
It's just the time wasn't quite right.
This might give it the push you need, though.
Assuming you're ready, that is.
Not just yet.
Now grow.
Trust me.
It won't be much longer.
This isn't for my sake.
But for Ru's.
My dear Ruko Kominato.
Black desire!
Tama!
Tama.
What?
Tama!
Tama.
Can you hear me?
That's not Ru.
Tama.
But I know that voice.
Better than Ru's.
Maybe better than my own.
It must have been from a long time ago.
You've finally come to see me.
Who...
Who are you?
Oh...
Hmm.
You poor thing.
All the pain she's put you through.
Ru is...
So cruel.
A wish to be together.
To never draw apart no matter what.
A dream that you believed in with all your heart.
I know you love Ru.
But she cares for her friends more than you.
No!
You got it all wrong!
Ru's not like that.
She said she'd be friends with me too.
Tama.
After this we were gonna go eat ice cream and dumplings.
And then I was gonna get a matching scrunchie so I could be like her other friends.
I'm so sorry.
It's true that Ru loves her friends.
She loves them so much that she lied to you.
And now she's going to become an L-Rig for them.
That's wrong!
We're all going home together after this.
So we have to win!
That won't happen.
Please listen to me.
Tama.
Try to remember.
The solution is easy.
You want to stop Ru from becoming an L-Rig, don't you?
You don't have to lose the fight.
You can refuse the wish at the very end.
Yuzuki said the same thing, right?
For a selector's wish to be fulfilled, the L-Rig must be in agreement.
But then, what'll happen to Ru's wish?
Win the battle and see.
Then you'll know her true feelings, and you'll see why I'm trying to protect you.
Protect me?
But only if you win.
Tama!
Are you able to get back up?
I'll find out her true feelings.
If you're still hurt, don't overdo it.
I'll fight, and I'll win the battle.
And then, it'll all be over.
Tama!
That's a good girl.
Hate to see you give up when it's just getting fun.
Drawing!
Enter charge!
Tama to level four!
No matter what happens after my wish, this is the last battle.
I don't know if it'll come true, or if everything will fall apart.
But we have to win!
This is the end!
What's that?
It's not an attack.
What's happening?
The battlefield's coming apart!
The roof!
Were we kicked out of the battlefield for some reason?
No, look. The sky. And it seems like they're still fighting.
Okay, Rue, what should I do for my next attack? Hurry!
It's so beautiful.
And I just noticed. You can see our apartment from here.
That does make me feel better.
Rue, what are you...
Thanks, Thalma.
You wanted me to see it one last time before the end, didn't you?
The end?
Bye, Grandma.
I love you.
Can you believe it, Iona? She thinks she's already won this.
She's the best.
She honestly is.
My Rue.
What's the next step, Thalma?
Before the last attack, an oath.
Okay, I'm ready.
That's right. Before my wish was granted, I took a oath with Hanuyo, too.
It seals the final contract between you and your L-Rate.
But wait!
If Thalma lost her memory, how does she know this?
Tell me what to say, and I'll say it.
Maybe she was lying to me.
She's not thinking about going back.
She never was.
She thinks the only way she can save her friends is to become an Elric.
She knew I wouldn't agree with this if she told me the truth.
She wants to sacrifice herself.
Thalma?
Please, just tell me what to say.
I accept the laws... the laws of...
I accept the laws of...
The laws of the...
Selector...
I accept the laws of the Selector.
And...
Thalma, thank you.
Ugh, this is taking forever.
The battle's almost over.
Can't we do something?
It's our turn, right?
Let's just finish them off.
You're in bloody slash.
Ready?
Yeah.
Use white help!
Ah!
What's going on?
Hang on, is this normal?
It's happening.
I knew it.
Yusuki, what are you looking at?
What's wrong?
You okay?
Don't worry.
I don't have a single regret.
Because no matter what happens,
this was the wish
that I chose for myself.
I'm happy to make it.
But why?
Ruko what, didn't she?
But the contract wasn't completed.
Huh?
They skipped the last part.
It goes,
And upon this sacred oath,
a new eternal girl shall be born.
What's wrong?
I can't do it.
Even if you earned your wish.
I can't let you turn into an Elring.
I can't let you.
Thalma!
What's happening?
Stop it!
Thalma, it's going away!
Finish the oath, please!
No!
Please!
This is wrong!
But I won the battle, didn't I?
Aw, don't look so surprised.
Iona's been ready to have her wish granted
for some time now.
She's won a whole ton of selector battles after all.
It's just we had to wait for a certain condition
to fall into place
before we can seal the deal.
Condition?
That's right.
But now the condition has been met.
Hope you're happy you've been waiting long enough.
That I have.
Not that I'm complaining.
But what about me?
Thalma!
Snap out of it!
Why won't you grant my wish?
Did something happen?
Thalma!
I accept.
The laws of the selector.
No.
You can't!
Damn it!
Please, just listen to me!
We have to turn everyone back to normal!
And upon this sacred oath,
a new eternal girl shall be born!
We...
The shadow of the age of the sky
The end of the day will open the dark
Wait... Yuna, you're...
Hmph...
No! Yurith!
Let's do this again sometime...
Miss Pain in the Ass!
Ruko... Tama...
Wait...
Weird as she...
Oh, this is gonna be fun...
Hi, Ruu
Oh, so good!
You really outdid yourself on the sauce this time, Grandma!
Ruu must be having fun and lost track of time!
She'll be fine, just eat already!
Not yet...
I made this just for her!
When we eat, we do it together!
You told me...
We'd do everything together, Ruu!
Tama!
Where'd you go?!
Yaaaaaa!
Foooo
Being with you is my wish.
Ah, we meet again, Miss Pain in the Ass.
So, when? Who's our first opponent?
I'm ready to fight!
Fight.
Was it because I did something mad?
But you're my friend, okay?
That's why.
Next, selector spread we cross.